ANASTASIA PEREZ

Full Stack Web Developer

DETAILS

ADDRESS

313 W WILLOW CREEK DR SARATOGA SPRINGS, 84045 United States

PHONE

4356304158

EMAIL

stasiperez85@gmail.com

LINKS

Portfolio -

https://stasiperez85.github.io/portfolio/

LinkedIn -

linkedin.com/in/anastasia-m-perez

Github -

https://github.com/Stasiperez85

SKILLS

Node.js

HTML & CSS

MySQL

JavaScript

MongoDB

PROFILE

I am an ambitious and self-motivated web developer with a strong desire to gain knowledge. I have experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MERN, and GraphQL. I look forward to joining a team to help me continue growing my skill set with a front/back end Web Development team. I've acquired a Certificate in Full Stack Web Development from the University of Utah. I loved jumping head first into the coding world and can't wait to continue my coding journey.

PROJECTS

Project 1: Movie Showings Website

See what movies are playing in your area!

Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bulma, jQuery, Moment.js, API

Website: https://github.com/mkelsch2000/Down-Hill-From-Here

Project 2: PetLink

Social media for your pets!

Technologies Used: Cloudinary React Node.js Express.js MongoDB and Mongoose ODM GraphQL JWT JavaScript React-Bootstrap HTML CSS

Website: https://serene-wildwood-60342.herokuapp.com/

GitHub: https://github.com/Darigay/PetLink_2.0

EDUCATION

Bachelors, Utah State University

Logan

Aug 2006 — May 2009

Graduation Cum Laude (with honor)

Emphasis in Communicative Disorders

Dec 2021 — May 2022

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Global Scheduling Coordinator, Zenger Folkman

Orem

May 2019 — Present

- · Coordinate and schedule all calls for Facilitators
- · Manage Company Calendars and ZOOM meeting links
- · Worked to ensure a positive and hassle-free customer experience.

Call Center Supervisor, Moduslink Global Solutions

Orem

May 2016 — May 2019

- · Train new hires
- · Motivate Team
- · Meet deadlines

Call Center Customer Service Supervisor, Hiring and Recruiting, Pondera Services

Logan

Oct 2009 — May 2016

- · Interviewed potential employers
- · Trained new hires
- · Managed 20 employees

REFERENCES

Damon Argyle

ZENGER FOLKMAN

dargyle@zfco.com 801-386-2087

Heidi Jolley

ModusLink and ZengerFolkman

hjolley@zfco.com 8013678665